A Guide to the Welford D. Taylor Collection on Sherwood Anderson, 1918-2006, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series IV: Images, Video, Audio, and Microfilm, 1970s-1991, n.d.
  - Subseries D: Microfilm, 1925-1931, n.d. (Box 3)
    - Roanoke Times articles in Sherwood Anderson's scrapbook regarding Kit Brandon
      Please note: Virginia Tech Special Collections does NOT house the original scrapbook from which these articles were filmed. It appears to be part of the Sherwood Anderson Papers held by the Newberry Library.
- Series V: Graphic Arts Materials, n.d.
  - J. J. Lankes Woodcuts (Prints and Photocopies) (Box 1, Folder 82, Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sherwood Anderson and Welford D. Taylor Bookplates (Box 1, Folder 83)